// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following will best describe a team?",
    answer: "d. Collaborative",
    options: [
      "a. Visionary",
      "b. Numerous",
      "c. Independent",
      "d. Collaborative"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following team members is responsible for gathering, processing, and performing statistical analyses of information related to the team’s ICT project?",
    answer: "b. Data Analyst",
    options: [
      "a. Content Writer and Editor",
      "b. Data Analyst",
      "c. Project Manager",
      "d. Web Developer"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "If you are good at writing and keen in identifying errors, which role is fitted for you?",
    answer: "a. Editor",
    options: [
      "a. Editor",
      "b. Data Analyst",
      "c. Web Developer",
      "d. Project Manager"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following Online platforms is categorized as Presentation or visualization?",
    answer: "a. Slideshare",
    options: [
      "a. Slideshare",
      "b. Isuu",
      "c. Facebook",
      "d. Weebly"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the first step in Project Management for ICT Content?",
    answer: "b. Initiating",
    options: [
      "a. Executing",
      "b. Initiating",
      "c. Planning",
      "d. Closing"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following online collaboration tools can be used as a to-do list for organizing the tasks of the team?",
    answer: "a. Trello",
    options: [
      "a. Trello",
      "b. Skype",
      "c. Tumblr",
      "d. Google Meet"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following platforms can be used for hosting ICT content for online publication?",
    answer: "b. Google Drive",
    options: [
      "a. Facebook Page",
      "b. Google Drive",
      "c. Kakao Talk",
      "d. WeChat"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following online collaboration tools can be used to store, organize, and edit ICT contents?",
    answer: "c. Google Drive",
    options: [
      "a. Prezi",
      "b. Zoom",
      "c. Google Drive",
      "d. Microsoft Teams"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "If you want to publish your ICT content on a blog site, which online platform is best to use?",
    answer: "a. WordPress",
    options: [
      "a. WordPress",
      "b. Twitter",
      "c. Facebook",
      "d. Prezi"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which tools can be used for online meeting?",
    answer: "d. Zoom",
    options: [
      "a. Google Drive",
      "b. Google Sheets",
      "c. Trello",
      "d. Zoom"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "If you want to share an online folder from Google Drive to limited people, which folder sharing mode would you choose?",
    answer: "c. Anyone with the link",
    options: [
      "a. Restricted",
      "b. Limited",
      "c. Anyone with the link",
      "d. Private"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which of the following is the correct sequence of Project Management of ICT Content?",
    answer: "b. Initiating→ Planning→ Executing→ Monitoring & Controlling→ Closing",
    options: [
      "a. Executing→ Initiating→ Planning→ Monitoring & Controlling→ Closing",
      "b. Initiating→ Planning→ Executing→ Monitoring & Controlling→ Closing",
      "c. Monitoring & Controlling→ Planning→ Initiating→ Executing→ Closing",
      "d. Planning→ Initiating→ Monitoring & Controlling→ Executing→ Closing"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a characteristic of a good collaborative tool or platform?",
    answer: "c. Has complex procedures",
    options: [
      "a. Appropriate to team’s goal",
      "b. Easy to use",
      "c. Has complex procedures",
      "d. Has good security features"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "You are reviewing videos created or collected by your teammates. You are in the process of choosing the best videos to be posted on your Filipino themed web portal. Which of the following will best describe the illustrated process?",
    answer: "a. Curating",
    options: [
      "a. Curating",
      "b. Planning",
      "c. Monitoring",
      "d. Web Designing"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which of the following statement is TRUE about online platforms and tools?",
    answer: "a. The team’s purpose for creating an ICT content is important in choosing online platforms and tools to be used.",
    options: [
      "a. The team’s purpose for creating an ICT content is important in choosing online platforms and tools to be used.",
      "b. Online platforms and tools separate the team from one another.",
      "c. There is no superior or best online platforms and tools.",
      "d. None of the above"
    ]
  },
];
